<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
  <title>EcoLiving Tips - Sustainable Living Made Simple</title>
  <link>https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/</link>
  <description>Discover actionable eco-friendly tips and sustainable living practices to reduce your carbon footprint. Simple, practical advice for a greener lifestyle in 2025.</description>
  <language>en-us</language>
  <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 12:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  <atom:link href="https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  
  <item>
    <title>Reduce Single-Use Plastics: Simple Swaps for a Cleaner Planet</title>
    <link>https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/#tips</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <guid>https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/#tips-plastic</guid>
    <description>Switch to reusable water bottles, shopping bags, and food containers to significantly reduce plastic waste. Learn about effective alternatives to common single-use plastic items.</description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Start Composting: Turn Kitchen Waste into Garden Gold</title>
    <link>https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/#tips</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <guid>https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/#tips-compost</guid>
    <description>Turn kitchen scraps and yard waste into nutrient-rich soil for your garden and reduce landfill waste. We explain how to start composting even in small spaces.</description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Energy-Efficient Lighting: Brighten Your Home While Saving Energy</title>
    <link>https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/#tips</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <guid>https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/#tips-lighting</guid>
    <description>Replace traditional bulbs with LED lights to save energy and reduce your electricity bill. Learn about the different options and how to choose the right lighting for each room.</description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Water Conservation: Simple Habits for a Sustainable Future</title>
    <link>https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/#tips</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <guid>https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/#tips-water</guid>
    <description>Install low-flow fixtures and be mindful of water usage to preserve this essential resource. Discover practical ways to reduce water consumption without sacrificing comfort.</description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Eat Local and Seasonal: Supporting Farmers and the Environment</title>
    <link>https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/#tips</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <guid>https://[YOUR-GITHUB-USERNAME].github.io/ecoliving-tips/#tips-food</guid>
    <description>Support local farmers and reduce transportation emissions by choosing locally grown, seasonal produce. We share tips for finding and preparing seasonal foods.</description>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>
